https://strategyassociation.site-ym.com/page/privacypolicy

ASP Website Privacy Policy - Association for Strategic Planning
This website uses cookies to store information on your computer. Some of these cookies are used for visitor analysis, others are essential to making our site function properly and improve the user experience. By using this site, you consent to the placement of these cookies. Click Accept to consent and dismiss this message or Deny to leave this website. Read our Privacy Statement for more.
Accept
Deny
Contact Us | Report Abuse | Sign In | Join
Toggle navigationMENUMembership About Us ASP Board and AdvisorsASP Strategic PlanHistory of the AssociationBenefitsCareer CenterAwards Richard Goodman Strategic PlanJanice Laureen Outstanding SerMember of the YearChapter of the YearDistinguished Service AwardHall of FameCommitteesIndividual ApplicationCorporate ApplicationStudent ApplicationStrategic Planning SocietyNewsletterPress ReleasesStart a ChapterAnnual General MeetingChapters & Communities Start a ChapterFind a GroupChapters AtlantaAustraliaBostonChicagoColoradoHondurasMembers At LargeNational Capital AreaNigeriaNorthern CaliforniaUgandaCommunities of Practice GovernmentNon Profit CommunitySPS Fellows Webinar WednesdayWomen in StrategyLeadership Chapter and Community LeadershipConference & Events 2020 Virtual Conference Series Conference Series AgendaConference Series RegistrationConference Series SponsorsEvents and WebinarsWorld Strategy Week 2016 RecordingsCertification About ASP Certification Who Holds Certification?News, Press Releases & FAQsASP Certification FrameworkStrategic Management ProfessionalStrategic Planning ProfessionalPopular LinksApply for Certification Determine Eligible Certification TypeExam Calendar and DeadlinesSubmit Your ApplicationCertification Fee StructureMake A PaymentPrepare for Exam Assess Your Readiness to CertifyWorkbooks and Study AidsHow to Form a Study GroupRegistered Education ProvidersBody of Knowledge FrameworkTake the Exam Testing Center LocationsTesting Center Fees and PaymentsRecertification RequirementsBecome a Registered Education ProviderLearn Body of Knowledge FrameworkGlobal WebinarsRecorded WebinarsBuy Store ProductsStrategy MagazineAlliance PartnersNonprofit ResourcesStrategy Books by MembersPast Annual Conferences 2019 Conference Presentations2018 Conference Presentations2017 Conference Presentations2016 Conference Presentations2015 Presentations2014 ASP Conference2013 ASP Conference Atlanta2012 Annual Conference2011 Annual Conference2010 Annual Conference2009 Annual Conference2008 Annual Conference2007 Annual Conference2006 Annual Conference
Edit This Favorite
Name:
Category:
Share:
Yes
No, Keep Private
ASP Website Privacy Policy
Share
|
ASP Privacy Policy
Association for Strategic Planning (ASP) is committed to protecting the privacy of personal information of its members, subject matter experts and all users of its services. This privacy policy has been prepared to affirm ASP’s commitment to maintaining high standards of confidentiality, to provide information on ASP’s practices concerning the collection, use and disclosure of your personal information and to comply with the Personal Information Protection and Electronic Documents Act (PIPEDA) and other applicable statutes, including the EU General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR).
ASP encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from the ASP website so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. ASP is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the ASP website.
1. Defining personal information
Personal information is any information about an "identifiable individual" that can be used to distinguish, identify or contact a specific individual. Business contact information such as information on your business card and certain publicly available information, such as names, addresses and telephone numbers as published in telephone directories are not considered personal information under federal legislation (PIPEDA). Information about corporations is not considered personal information.
2. Collection of personal information
If you request information, products or services from ASP, we will collect name and contact details including address(es), mailing preference, telephone and fax numbers, email address, and language preference.
We collect no personal information about you unless you choose to provide that information to us. We do not use techniques that collect personal information about anyone without their knowledge. We only collect personal information about individuals when they specifically and knowingly provide it to us, for example when they apply for membership or complete an event registration form. You may also provide us with your credit card information in order to pay for items purchased. We collect this information only to set up your account, process the order, and provide you with the services you are purchasing. We do not store credit card information for later use.
ASP collects and retains information about your transaction history when you use ASP services and various programs. You may, at any time, ask to have this information removed or deleted - please reach out to executivedirector@strategyassociation.org in order to have this done.
3. ASP Website
Personal information is only collected when an individual voluntarily submits his or her information such as in an online membership application form, meeting registration form or an online survey. The personal information collected in this manner is subject in full to the Privacy Policy contained in this document.
If you do nothing during your visit but browse through the website, read pages, or download information, we will not gather or store personal information. Our web server collects statistical data about visitor information, specifically through the use of Google Analytics, used only in aggregate. This tracking system does not record personal information about individuals or link this information to any personal data collected.
4. Use of information
ASP commits to you that individual information will be used to establish and maintain responsible relationships with you, to provide you with products, services and support, and to respond to member needs. Your personal information will be used to provide you with the specific transaction that you applied for or services requested in the application you submitted.
One of ASP’s primary objectives is disseminating information to its members. The achievement of ASP’s objectives involves, among other things, providing you with information about products and services that ASP believes are of interest you.
Your personal information may also be made available to other members of ASP, if you so choose, through our online membership directory. You can make your information available by adjusting the preferences in your profile. You can change these preferences at any time. The main purpose of this is to facilitate member networking and at no point will the information displayed in the member directory be shared with any third party or non-member of the association.
5. Consent by individuals
The information you provide to ASP — such as your name, address, etc. — allows ASP to inform you about events and activities and to notify you of issues, events or special offers which may be of interest to you. By becoming a member or by requesting information or registering for events offered by ASP, you are giving ASP permission to contact you by way of the information you provide. If you choose to sign up for our newsletter or any other communication from us, you can unsubscribe from future mailings at any time by clicking the unsubscribe links at the bottom of the email. If you prefer to opt-out by a different means please contact ASP’s Office at executivedirector@strategyassociation.org.
6. Disclosure of personal information
ASP may share aggregate information about its members and customers — not individual data or personal contact information — with sponsors, potential sponsors and other parties to help them better understand ASP members and their interests.
Such aggregate information is used to give ASP demographic data about its members in order to improve the organization and the programs and services we provide.
7. Security of information
ASP endeavors to maintain appropriate safeguards and adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respect to our offices and information storage facilities so as to prevent any unauthorized access, disclosure, copying, use, or modification of personal information. Safeguards include securing physical documents and technological measures by way of secure access and encryption. ASP employees are authorized to access personal information based only on their need to deal with the information for the reason(s) for which it was obtained. Safeguards are in place to ensure that the information is not disclosed or shared more widely than is necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was gathered. We also take measures to ensure the integrity of this information is maintained and to prevent its being lost or destroyed.
8. Storage Outside of Canada
Your personal information may be used or stored by us or our service providers outside of Canada. We require that our service providers safeguard your personal information, however, if your personal information is used or stored outside of ASP, it will also be subject to the laws of the country in which it is used or stored.
9. Updates to this Statement
ASP encourages you to periodically review this statement to be informed of how we are protecting your information.ASP reserves the right to make changes to this Privacy Policy without advance notice. The revised Policy will be posted online and effective immediately upon posting. Your use of the ASP website indicates that you accept our Privacy Policy. Your continued visits to the ASP website after changes are posted to this Policy will signify your acceptance of those changes.
10. Contact Us
If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or about ASP’s information handling practices, please contact us at executivedirector@strategyassociation.org.
Updated May 15, 2018
Sign In
Remember Me
Forgot your password?Haven't joined yet?
Latest News
more
7/22/2020Advancing Social Justice through Strategic Planning and Action Webinar Recording- Free for Everyone!
6/10/2020Webinar Wednesday Presents: Leading through Chaos - What is Strategy Now?
5/28/2020Strategy Magazine has arrived!
Calendar
more
10/19/2020ASP National Capital Area (NCA) Presents: Developing Meaningful KPIs to Measure what Matters10/20/2020ASP Australia Presents: Why Strategies Fail, Even Though Everyone Plans to Succeed10/21/2020ASP Webinar Wednesday Presents: Strategy Implementation in the Public Sector: Initial Survey Results
Featured Members
membership | communities | events | certification | award | knowledge center | members | privacy policy
Please note that this address may require additional postage.
Please check with your local post provider for details.
Legal
